Kenneth Basjan

About Me

I am a software developer proficient in C#, Java, Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MERN Stack, and WordPress. I specialise in front-end development and own Weberu, an SMMA providing digital services to boost revenue and brand awareness for businesses around the world.

Work Experience



Weberu (SMMA)

Founder

November 2021 to Present.

Weberu is a social media marketing agency that offers services such as social media management, content creation, influencer marketing, and social media advertising.

- Developed and executed innovative social media campaigns for a range of clients, delivering measurable results and achieving client objectives.
- Built and managed a team of social media experts, overseeing all aspects of the business, including strategy, operations, and client management.



UVU Africa: CapaCiTi Division - ABSA Cohort 1

Junior Software Developer Intern January 2023 to July 2023

- Developing web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, and Java, working with a team of experienced developers to create high-quality, user-friendly software solutions.
- Contributing to the development of multiple software projects, using agile development methodologies to deliver results efficiently and effectively.
- Demonstrating strong problem-solving skills and attention to detail, identifying and resolving issues quickly and efficiently to ensure that software solutions are delivered on time and to the highest quality standards.



//Software Developer //Entrepreneur

Contact Info

- in linkedin.com/in/kenneth-basjan/
- github.com/Abbbtle
- instagram.com/abbbtle/
- kenneth.basjan@younglings.
 - https://portfolio-78029.web.app

Relevant Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Java
- C#
- Python
- ReactJS
- Tailwind CSS
- Django
- AJAX
- JQuery
- PostgreSQL
- BootStrap
- WordPress (Elementor)
- SEO
- Social Media Management
- Content Writing

younglings Younglings Africa

Software Developer Intern: ABSA Cohort 1

July 2023 to Present

- Developing web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, and Java, working with a team of experienced developers to create high-quality, userfriendly software solutions.
- Contributing to the development of multiple software projects, using agile development methodologies to deliver results efficiently and effectively.
- Demonstrating strong problem-solving skills and attention to detail, identifying and resolving issues quickly and efficiently to ensure that software solutions are delivered on time and to the highest quality standards.



Empire Partner Foundation

Fullstack Web Developer

October 2023 - January 2024

- Crafted a robust fullstack web application collaboratively using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, AJAX, jQuery, Python, Django, and Bootstrap in a team of three developers.
- Enhanced skills during tenure at Younglings Africa, gaining valuable experience at Empire Partner Foundation.
- Conducted efficient daily standup meetings online.
- Utilized Microsoft Planner and various other Microsoft tools for meticulous planning.
- Prepared a User Stories Document outlining each component's functionality, appearance, and user experience.
- Developed a comprehensive pitch deck and ERD diagram to streamline the development process.
- Documentation significantly facilitated the two-sprint development phase over four weeks.

Education History



National Diploma in Information Technology:

Software Development

Central University of Technology:

Bloemfontein Campus

2016 - 2019



Creative Business 101 for Videographers

ORMS Cape Town School for Photography

2021

Volunteer Work, Awards, Affiliations, and Interests



ISKCON Cape Town

2019 to Present

I serve at the ISKCON Cape Town temple as a brahmana priest, teacher / guide, musician, cook, and IT specialist. The goal of this project is to provide a safe space for young and old individuals who are are searching for God and need a space in order to; meditate, perform yoga, eat healthy vegetarian food, and dive deep into spiritual philosophy.

References

Miss Afika Maliwa

Company: UVU Africa - CapaCiTi

Role: Candidate Manager Phone: +27 78 692 2178

Email: afika.maliwa@capaciti.org.za

Mr Shadly Frans

Company: UVU Africa - CapaCiTi

Role: Mentor

Phone: +27 72 5757147

Email: shadly.frans@capaciti.org.za

Mr Cameron Davids

Company: Younglings Role: Candidate Manager Phone: +27 69 710 5387

Email: cameron.davids@younglings.africa

Mr Brandon September

Company: UVU Africa - CapaCiTi

Role: Mentor

Phone: +27 79 477 0660

Email: brandon.september@capaciti.org.za

Mr Gokulesh Das

Company: ISKCON Cape Town

Role: Temple President Phone: +27 72 416 0853

Miss Ofentse Leseilane

Company: Empire Partner Foundation

Role: Software Developer Phone: +27 83 564 5840

Email: ofentse@empirepartnerfoundation.org